[Music]
the war in Afghanistan against the
Taliban and Al-Qaeda exactly 14 years
later to the date 14 years my God this
war is officially a
teenager right this war now has two
things to worry about never ending and
having its mom walk in on it jerking
off Afghanistan oh Mom no Mom go go go
the caption referred to African slaves
as
workers
workers this is insane I mean there's a
reason slave ships were called slave
ships they weren't car
Pools Ben Carson was talking about
Popeyes and he said uh the popey's
organization no black person says
popey's
organization I don't know where let's go
to popey's
organization purchas and purchase some
chicken yeah let's get let's get two
piece in a biscuit from the popey
nobody says that hey America Larry
Wilmore here if you like the nightly
show on Comedy Central like us on
Facebook too just don't poke me I do not
like being poked you can Candy Crush me